And finally, James Comey was arraigned today
regarding federal charges of lying to Congress.
You know, just for fun,
they should give him this many days.
Oh.
Yeah.
So apparently Democrats have a new plan
to win back young men.
And it's not inventing a time machine
to undo the last eight years
where dudes wore mumus
and a dead guy was elected president.
The party is testing everything
from beer ads to left-wing influencers.
In other words,
they're trying to rebrand a bad product
instead of putting out a good one.
They're even trying something called gym outreach.
Yeah, gym outreach,
which by the way,
was my stage name when I made those films
to pay my way through community college.
Those were the days.
Democrat operatives are paying
left-leaning fitness influencers
to create online content.
Think about that.
They're paying guys to pretend
that they're masculine liberals.
And here I thought that was what Hollywood was for.
But the same guys who called physical fitness
white supremacy now pretend
that they like the bench press.
Finally, a transition
that doesn't make you cut anything off
except the carbs.